[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Target Zoe
confirmed dead.
I asked Ching He's chairman, Thackery Huang, for a favor.
This will save your life.
CHING HE TEMPLE
If you're ever in danger, use this to contact Ching He.
There's key evidence that can control the Hsuehs.
Hello?
Gerald Chen said
if my life was in danger,
I should make this call.
Please.
Save me and my daughter.
I got it.
I'll send someone right away.
THE FIXERS
FAKE, FORSAKEN, FRAUD
Zoe is still alive. This isn't just bad for Yeh Yueh Tong.
It's also a threat
to the Hsueh family.
-I won't harm her. -I know you won't.
At least not now.
What do you mean?
Who knows if you will bring Zoe home
to score points?
You've been using me to find Zoe from the start.
Right?
Since I was a child, I've never listened to my dad.
He can't stand the sight of me.
You're right.
If I bring Zoe home,
he'll think highly of me.
Right?
-What will you do? -What about you?
Madam Fan sent someone to kill Gerald.
I won't let this slide.
You're declaring war on the entire Yeh Yueh Tong.
Even if it's possible, imagine the fallout.
What's there to consider?
Gerald is already dead.
You don't need to follow him to the grave.
This is my own life.
-I don't need your advice. -Dying won't bring him back.
-Is it worth it? -Have you ever wanted to protect anyone?
BROTHER: DAD ISN'T WELL. COME TO THE HOSPITAL QUICKLY.
How's Dad doing now?
Doctor said it's liver cancer.
It has metastasized.
This is bad, and you're only telling me now?
He told me not to tell you, so you wouldn't worry.
He isn't doing well today.
Try not to talk back to him.
Dad, are you okay?
I'm okay.
I just had chemotherapy.
I don't feel very well.
Don't tell the public
about my illness.
At a time like this,
politics still matters more than your health?
Why did you hide it from me?
What about you?
When did you join Ching He?
Did it ever occur to you
that Thackery asked you to join Ching He for a reason?
By working for him,
anytime, anywhere,
you become a pawn that can threaten the Hsueh family.
I know what I'm doing.
If anything does happen, I won't drag the Hsueh family into it.
Do you think
I only care about your brother?
You are my son too.
I keep wondering.
Did I not show you how much I cared?
Did I invest too much in your brother?
Is that why you're doing this to prove yourself?
I was too strict with you.
Now that I think about it…
I never gave you the chance to show me what you can do.
You did this
because you didn't want the world to learn who I am.
It would embarrass the Hsueh family, right?
If that's what I cared about,
why would I have kept you around?
I failed your mom.
Before your mom passed away,
I promised her
I would raise you well.
I only hope that you will think carefully
before you do anything.
Think about our family.
I am getting old.
I don't have much time left
to be with you two.
From now on…
you and your brother must look after each other.
All right?
Are you okay?
You knew, right?
That I joined Ching He as a fixer.
How did you find out?
Dad didn't say who told him.
William is dead. Did you know that?
I saw it on the news. Suicide by carbon monoxide poisoning.
You didn't invest with him, right?
He helped launder a ton of cash from the Hsin Nan project, didn't he?
How did you know?
I have my sources.
That project is a huge cash cow.
Everyone in the party took a piece.
Dad's influence in the party was weakening.
He couldn't offend those heavyweights.
He had no choice but to play along.
Why ask Yeh Yueh Tong to kill Zoe and her family?
Zoe's husband, Hsu Ming-yi, knew about this.
He demanded a hefty sum
and wanted Dad's support to run for the legislature.
Hsu Ming-yi even found out
that Dad had you with a student.
He blackmailed him.
Dad wanted to protect you
and the Hsueh family.
He really was out of options.
So he asked Yeh Yueh Tong for help.
He's in poor health now.
Don't bring these things up to him.
I'm going to stay with him for a while. What about you?
I'll stay a little longer.
A new type of drug was found at the scene.
It may cause the heart to stop temporarily.
Users may even become unconscious and appear dead.
Sir, do you have any left?
Sorry, we're closed.
Long time no see.
SHEN: BEN IS IN TROUBLE
GERALD CHEN, YEH YUEH TONG
MISSING, KIDNAPPED, DRUGS
In the beginning,
you joined Yeh Yueh Tong
in order to look for Gerald.
At the time,
I knew
he had trained a good apprentice.
Release him.
Where is Zoe?
You know what will happen
if I pull it out, don't you?
You already sent someone to kill Gerald.
So why'd you ask me to look for him?
We never found his body.
I was going to use you to see if he was alive.
To my surprise, I discovered
Zoe still lives.
If you have the guts, kill me.
Let him go.
You are just as capable as Gerald.
But one slight misstep,
and you would turn on me.
Where is Zoe?
Don't… don't tell her.
Even if you tell her,
she won't let us go.
You should know very well
how long he can hold on.
I don't know.
I never expected
Zoe's life to be more important to you than his.
I really don't know.
Please.
Let him go.
Let them go.
Louis Hsueh.
The Hsueh family's younger son. I've heard great things about you.
Let the two of them go,
and I will drop this matter.
Is everyone at Ching He so cocky?
If news of Yeh Yueh Tong's incompetence reached my dad's ears,
what would he think?
Are you speaking to me on behalf of the Hsueh family
or Ching He?
What do you think?
You must remember.
I am the one standing by the Hsueh family.
Mina,
he met his fate because of your betrayal.
Gerald…
Is Gerald really dead?
This isn't your fault.
You… you must move on.
Live… well.
When I see Gerald,
I… I will tell him that.
The stall downstairs…
Okay.
I know.
Don't leave.
Hello? Lix's Express.
Can you pick up a package now?
It's safe. Go ahead.
Why did you go?
The chairman was looking for you.
Ben is dead.
What?
Ben is dead?
We didn't find Gerald, but we found Zoe.
I just rescued Mina from Madam Fan.
But I was still too late.
How did you two find Zoe?
Gerald was sent by Yeh Yueh Tong to kill Zoe.
But he couldn't do it, so he faked her death.
Now Madam Fan knows Zoe is alive.
She'll get rid of her for good.
No wonder the chairman wanted me to protect Zoe.
I'm heading to her.
How did he find out?
He didn't say much.
Let me bring her back first.
Okay. Be careful.
Yeh Yueh Tong won't just let this go.
Don't worry. They'll have to get in line if they want to take my life.
Felix?
Zoe is fine.
Felix is taking her back to Ching He Temple.
How did Ching He know where Zoe was?
Do you think I know?
Get some rest first.
Get on a plane tonight and leave.
Who says I'm leaving?
Do you think Madam Fan will spare you?
She killed the only family I had left.
I will make her pay.
We don't even know why Ching He wants Zoe.
Stepping into this fight only puts you in more danger.
Are you worried about me
or that I'll drag the Hsuehs down?
Think what you want.
It's your life.
I don't want to have to collect your body later.
I will take care of my own business.
I won't trouble you.
I thought you never leave a trace.
Louis knows that we hired Yeh Yueh Tong.
Don't worry.
I will clean this up.
I won't leave any loose ends.
Regarding Thackery, I've arranged everything.
I hope you won't make any more mistakes.
What's wrong?
It's the groundbreaking ceremony.
I've arranged everything. Don't worry.
I…
probably won't make it
to the day you become mayor.
Dad,
I've arranged for the best doctor.
If they can't treat you here, we'll go abroad.
You will get better.
I will make sure
you watch me reach the top,
not just become mayor.
I never have to worry about you.
It is always your brother.
As long as he stays with Ching He,
I cannot rest easy.
Don't worry.
After all, he is still a part of the Hsueh family.
Has he ever seen himself that way?
He joined Ching He behind my back.
If you hadn't stopped me,
I would have…
Dad.
Don't think about it, Dad.
Your health matters most now.
Knowing Louis,
forcing him to quit now
will only push him further away.
I'm thinking, let him stay with Ching He.
Maybe that could help us in the future.
All those years of effort weren't wasted on you.
I have to thank you for cooperating with me.
Get some rest.
Just leave the rest to me.
You… you won't…
harm your brother, will you?
He is my own brother.
How could I possibly harm him?
You haven't offered incense at Ching He Temple in so long.
Last time I set foot in the main hall,
my dad was still alive.
This time around,
I cannot come unprepared.
What are you praying for this time?
I pray that God will bring me justice.
Everything I did
was to protect Ching He.
Wasn't that also true
of my dad and me?
Fixer Lunar,
anything that disrupts the balance of the world,
no matter how well-intentioned, is wrong.
All I know is,
I won't let anyone
take away what's mine again.
Should I see you out?
I should be the one doing that.
I came to say goodbye to you.
Sir, the mayor reportedly holds
some of the bribe money that Mr. Chao Ming-cheng accepted.
What do you say to this?
I can't comment on that.
It is under investigation.
But I believe that for a politician,
integrity is the most important thing.
Will the party take any action against Mr. Chao?
Should the mayor apologize to the public?
What action will the party take?
Sir, could you…
Mr. Huang,
we're working on the bribery case against Mr. Chao Ming-cheng.
We believe you are involved.
You need to come with us.
This is a search warrant.
We will now search Ching He Temple.
-Go in and search. -Yes, sir.
There were new developments in the bribery case against Chao.
Investigators launched a second wave of searches today
targeting Thackery Huang, who chairs Ching He, an influential local group.
Thackery Huang was suspected of being an intermediary in the bribery.
He was escorted to the police station earlier…
I want to talk to you in private.
Did you get Thackery arrested?
Yes.
Are you helping Madam Fan seize Ching He?
Ching He belonged to Madam Fan.
How is it seizing?
You're supporting Madam Fan.
It can't just be to cover up what Dad did, right?
I often say you're far smarter than I am.
Dad just doesn't believe it.
What is your goal?
I want Ching He's Primordial Files.
You want the secret files?
That's right.
The former Fixer Celestial, Madam Fan's dad,
hid the Primordial Files
in a secret room in Kuang Ming Chamber.
Only Madam Fan knows how to unlock the room.
Not even Thackery.
So you want to get the Primordial Files from Madam Fan.
Madam Fan knows what Dad has done.
If she reclaims Ching He,
she will have the Hsueh family by the throat.
She could turn on us anytime.
So we must get to the Primordial Files before her.
That way, we can control both sides of the law.
Neither Ching He nor Yeh Yueh Tong
can threaten the Hsueh family.
Is that necessary?
You don't have to help me.
But if you don't, those you care about,
those you want to protect, could be in danger.
First, eliminate Thackery.
Then, Madam Fan.
As for Ching He,
I hope you will be in charge of it.
Me, in charge of Ching He?
Only by holding real power at the top
can you protect those you care about.
When I become mayor,
and you control Ching He,
you will be in the dark,
and I in the light.
If we unite as brothers,
who could threaten us?
Howie,
does your dad really have Parkinson's?
He told me himself.
He told me not to tell you.
You know he likes to talk nonsense all the time.
I saw his bag of pills.
Howie, listen to me.
From now on, I will take good care of your dad.
You just focus on your studies.
What are you talking about?
I can take care of him too, okay?
It's all on your dad's stubbornness.
He could've just been honest about the necklace.
His behavior made me think he was cheating.
Hey.
Tell him you found it out on your own.
Don't say I told you.
I know.
Like two silly boys.
Ridiculous.
Darn it, Felix.
Forgot to bring his keys again.
What is it?
That car must have broken down.
The road ahead is blocked.
Wait in the car.
Is Felix Chiang here?
What is this for?
I am his business acquaintance.
A business acquaintance?
I… haven't heard him mention anything about doing business.
Is he not here?
No, he's not.
How about this?
Give me your number.
I'll ask him to call you.
Is your son not here either?
He's not here either.
He's out studying with his classmates.
You've lived in this house for over 20 years, right?
Since we got married.
We've never moved.
How sentimental.
You two must be close.
But that's hard to say.
It seems like he's hiding a lot from you.
I told Felix I call the shots in this house.
Whatever mess he's made outside, I don't care, nor do I want to know.
If there's nothing else, please leave.
I have something important
to ask Felix.
Dad, hurry back.
There's trouble.
HOWIE, TAKE CARE OF YOUR MOM. TELL HER I'LL BE BACK SOON!
I'm gonna take a look. You be careful.
Okay.
Sorry. I've called roadside assistance.
My son has a high fever. I need to get to the hospital.
It won't take much longer. I called over two hours ago.
We'll go to the ER.
Please.
You must protect my daughter.
CHING HE TEMPLE
Give this…
to Thackery Huang.
The video
has to do with…
CHING HE TEMPLE
…the Hsueh family.
Subtitle translation by: Hannah Liu